Hello friends, my name is Sachin and
yes, today I have brought a new video for you again,
so friends, today we are going to talk
about the recently launched Complete Health Insurance 2.0 of this slot,
so friends, earlier there used to be Complete
Health Insurance of Rs. 1000, but due to the
increase in the flood that came in this month of November 2020, it has been
upgraded and made the 2.0 version, so today
we are going to discuss about this in detail
and after all I will
tell you about all the points,
why the plan is better than before and
what new features have been set in it, so
friends, first of all if we talk about the hot, then the company has
divided this new version into four points, in which the first plan is
our Help Shield, the second is called
Help Sheet Plus, the third line comes
for Health and the fourth line comes Health Tips
Plus, so friends, these are categories of four new plans,
all of them have some new
advances, so what we will do is
review it one by one,
today we will first review Health
and after that gradually  We
will review all four Prem, all four videos you will get to
see on my channel,
so first of all let us talk
about everything, so the benefits of this line,
friends, first of all is that
you can buy any Jasmine worth Rs 3 lakh to Rs 50 lakh in
it, that is,
after this, three lakh, five lakh, seven
lakh, ten lakh and in this way,
you can take a policy under it for Rs 15, 2050, free and
post-graduation friends, if we talk about this, then
when you were not admitted in the hospital, then the
expenses before 30 days and after that,
when you have come home after being discharged, then there are
expenses till that day, if we
talk about the room rent limit,
friends, here you get a single private air
conditioned room, in which there is no
amount of caffeine, now there is a single
private air conditioned loop control, you can
go to any hospital and get it,
see, talking about the treatment,
friends, earlier there used to be some
specific procedures here, which were
around one and a half hundred  It used to be around but
now the company has changed it to all day care
position here, so now you can get
all the day care procedures done by any doctor in
your day care here, then
you will get that
facility here. Talking about no claim bonus,
friends, you will get ten percent no
claim bonus here. This year also you have
not taken any claim, so if you had taken a loan of Rs
10 lakh and your ten
percent no claim bonus was Rs 1 lakh on that,
then next year the
total policy of Rs 10 lakh plus Rs 1 lakh no claim bonus in
your policy will become Rs 11 lakh. It keeps increasing in this manner,
which is the maximum fifty
percent, that is,
after 5 years, if you have not made any choice, then it will become Rs
15 lakh.
Talking about reset benefit, friends, this is a
very good unique point of this policy,
which you should understand well, that
also happens to be
friends that if
you have owned Sims Hair  A policy of 10 lakhs was
taken and there are four members in a family, that is,
if I talk about 1 Kar General Assembly,
here there are two adults and two
children, then what is there here is that the
recent benefit tells you that you
can take it for unlimited times, that is,
if the second one is over, then you can take it again for 10
lakh 30 thousand 12 thousand 10 lakh 34 thousand five times, such
unlimited times, but here the
condition is that you
cannot take it in the same plan within the seven choices, suppose if
someone takes a policy for heart attack
and the bill comes
for 10 lakh rupees and in the same year he gets
admitted for attack again, then you will
not get that claim, but if he gets
admitted there due to some other reason, that is, due to kidney problem, liver problem, then he will get that
claim again, along with this, if your family
member, suppose he has an email address,
his friend, 10 lakh people have sent him Bigg Bank benefits.  Boss,
if their wife needs 10 lakh rupees then
she will get it. If
one of her children needs Rs. 10 lakh
this year then that too will be available. If
other children also need 10 lakh rupees once a year
then that too will be available here
friends. That means you
can also see it in this way that
a recent benefit of ₹10 lakh is available here for everyone.
Okay friends, so let's move ahead, today
we will talk about this treatment here
like Ayurveda, Siddha, Unani,
this type of treatment, if you are given any treatment
in the hospital and that is a rule from the
government then you
get its facility here also. Moving ahead
friends, let's talk about ambulance cover, that is
also a very good unique feature of theirs that here
you are given one percent time allowance.
If suppose here you have
taken one percent ₹5000 in the policy of Malik Tapasya from five sports,
then will you get it in this
that you will get up to ₹5000. Answer a question.  You
can take cover for one ambulance,
whereas you will see in other policies, here the
maximum is up to Rs 1500, 2000 or ₹100. Here the maximum
is 10,000, meaning if you have Rs 10 lakh, then you
can claim from the company for hospitalization even on Rs 10,000.
If we talk about entries, friends, then
any healthy person from 18 years can take it here
and there is no limit. Here, if you are 65
years old, 70 years old, 75 years old,
if you have a medical kit, then you can take this policy.
Here, if we talk about dependent child
or new born baby cover, then if
any new born baby is born in your family, then
you
can add him/her under this policy within 921 years
or if you have a dependent child, then there is a cover for him/her,
here till the age of 21,
you can keep your child in school.
Friends, the
best thing about ICC that I find in it  There is that claim
service guarantee. These people make you click on your browser and say
that our film service
is guaranteed, but we will settle your cashless claim within four hours
and the second
reimbursement claim within 14 days.
If we are not able to do this, then
we will charge you a penalty. So far, from what
I have seen in the entire industry, there is
no one-time service guarantee anywhere.
People claim that the claim is processed in 30 minutes, 1 hour,
2 hours or 90% of
our claims are processed in this time, but they do
not use the guarantee.
Talking about policy discount, friends,
if you buy a 2-year plan here,
you will get a 10 percent discount on your second year premium.
Similarly, if you buy a 3-year plan here,
you will get a 15 percent discount on the third year
premium. Friends, health checkup is
available to you every year here. Under health checkup, you get
some listed
checkups which you can
also get by going to a diagnostic center.  You can get it done or you can also call the
members of the diagnosis centre to
your home and they will do the
checkup at your home. So,
in every policy, two coupons are available which are
for two adults and they can redeem it every year.
If we talk about these points, friends, then they
are available on balance points here. Suppose you
participate in a marathon or any
test, you have
participated in swimming or have joined your gym,
if you share its bill or its proof
here, then according to every category,
you get points here
and that point increases by 25 paise and
you can encash that point
in OPD benefit,
this money is signed in your policy and you can
go to the OPD and
avail its benefit in cashless reimbursement mode. Let's
talk further, friends, there are search
expenses, this cover was not there earlier in such a way
that if you had to
take any organ from anyone.  If it is there then the
company will bear its expenses here and they will do this. Now let's talk about Sudha
Sum Assured
's normal transplantation,
friends, it is like Dance Laddu Mission Hospital chain that
if suppose the patient
is not in a condition to be admitted inside the hospital
or if there is
no bed available in all the hospitals in your vicinity, then
in this condition you are provided a notification that
all the facilities are provided at your home itself
like a hospital, so
that facility is available here.
Talking about ambulance cover, friends, which was
not there earlier, in such a situation, it has been
added here and it is up to the sum insured, that is,
suppose you have taken a policy of
₹ 1000000, then here you will
also get this ambulance cover, that too will be of Rs 1000000.
So friends, what the company is saying is that
this cover is not covered, that is,
if suppose you have taken a policy of ₹ 2 lakh or  If you
use the cover of Tilak Repair Ambulance, then
if you take a policy of your total 10 lakhs, then it will
not be included in it. This is
your insurance cover now, your base will remain the same. Okay, and ₹10
here, this ambulance cover is for
all the additional time, friends, there is
also its protector. This
means no claim bonus. They have to
change the definition language a little. So
here, if any of your claims does
not go above fifty thousand in a year, then
what will happen, the company will concentrate it
and will not give you no claim bonus next year,
but there is an inbuilt feature in this plan,
you will not have to pay extra money for this, it will happen in it
that if
suppose your claim is below 50 thousand, then
you were to get this ten percent no
claim bonus, you will get it, okay,
and due to this, those policies will
increase a little. Talking about tele-consultation,
friends, this
also seems to be their best unique feature because
in today's times of corruption or considering the convenience of the people.
Nowadays, people are either not going to the
doctor
or they don't want to visit the hospital.
Here, they have provided a television
station of the doctor which is
available for you 24*7, that is, all day and night. You should have an Oil Tech
Care app, you
will download that app and there is
an option of tele consultation with doctor, if
you click on it, then
a doctor's college will appear in front of you, who will be an MBA
certificate, so you
can tell him about your problems and he will
send you his prescription on email, saying
that you should take these medicines or you should do this,
then Rupa, so
friends, this voice video chat option
is available to you, which is an
investment free feature in your policy, friends, here the
facility of dietitian nutrition consultation is also available, if you want to take
a consultation in which you
want to maintain your diet or you
want to take nutrition supplements, then
you can consult a doctor there,
that too is free of cost, friends, a
good
and I  They have added that ambulance
assistance in it,
if their ambulance assistant
service is available in your city, which you
can check by going to their website, then what will happen there is that
you will call the ambulance assistant there, then the
doctor there will automatically assess you whether you
really need emergency ambulance service at this time,
if that is the case and the
facility is available in your city, then
that ambulance service will be provided to you on a cashless basis,
you do
not need to make any payment there,
generally you pay for the ambulance service
and after that this reinforcement
comes in your account, but here the
company has given an ambulance, if you
go to their Apple and click there, then the
important balance assistant will come to your home
and that too on a question basis, let's
talk about this settings open friends,
suppose any of your members gets a
critical illness like cancer,
your dial has
come to this, okay or anyone stops you,
brain tumor type, means it is difficult
English, okay, if any such  Situations arise
and you want to
get a single opinion from a doctor about whether
we should get this treatment or this surgery for an aeroplane. If we don't want to, then
those decisions will be made. Now, we have a
level within this, so you can avail the benefit of this as well. The
company will not charge you any additional fee for this either. So,
friends, all the
covers that I have told you so far are
invested in this plane, for this the company will
not charge you any additional fee,
but it will ask for the one that I am
telling you, for this the company will charge you some
additional fee and these services will also be
added to your policy. Let's
first talk about the Someshwar Protector.
Friends, here the Swami Chhod Protector says that whatever sum you have insured from me, so
friends, what happens from
time to time, you are
also seeing that inflation keeps increasing.
If today I have taken a policy of Rs 5 lakh, then
why won't it be the same after the next five years? The inflation, the
hospital expenses, the
treatment cost, all these are increasing day by day.
So keeping this in mind, the company has added
a new addition in it called Submit Tax
Protractor. What happens in it is
our government organization, it is called
Central Statistical Organization. It declares
a Consumer Price Index every year and on
this thing,
now it is this much, that is, the companies say
that we have fixed a separate margin of six percent on it, so
suppose
you have taken a policy of 10 lakhs, then its
six percent is Rs. 7000,
if you have taken a policy for 5 girls, then its six
percent is ₹3000 there, this will be
added to your base insurance cost every year, that is, if you have a
policy of ₹500, then next
year it will become 5 lakh 30 thousand, then it will become 5 lakh
60 thousand, in the same way it will keep
increasing gradually, your no claim bonus is a different
thing, that will also keep increasing and this
also
increases, your no claim bonus will
increase, so friends, many such
situations also come with us that  Suppose
you have all your regular claims and
in this situation the company never increases your purse.
If you have
taken such a product then what can you do? Even if you
give up your impatience, it will keep
increasing gradually. So I would say that this is a
good thing. You should definitely
think about it. Let's talk
about the plan product.
Friends, there are many such things
which you should mention as not visible in your idea.
Not visible means that
friends, like Bigg Boss money,
admission charges, etc., which
earlier insurance companies did not give.
If I talk about a bill of Rs 1 lakh, then
every customer had to pay Rs 3000
from his pocket. But today
it has reduced considerably. And if you get a
big bill, then even in that, if
you have taken this plan, then
you do not need to pay even Rs 1 in the hospital.
Your hundred
percent plan will be settled completely by the company.
Whatever you had to
pay initially to TCS or anything
else, not all of that, but you will have to do it here.
Friends, there is a cover here which is
not available in the market right now. It is easily available
in 12 companies, but there are more conditions in it.
But to be a little clear,
this condition has been kept here, Worldwide cover.
Friends, if your plan is
above 10 lakhs, okay, if it is 10 lakhs or
above 10 lakhs, then you
can take Worldwide cover here, including
US and Canada. You
can get your treatment done anywhere in the world, but the condition in this is
that your travel period should be for
45 days, that is, if
you went on January 1st, then
you can stay here till February 15th. So,
whatever expenses are incurred in this, the company will decide on your
basis. If you took plain treatment here, please
support. If you had to get
treatment done in India and you know
that the treatment is better in that specific country
and you
should get it done there, and if you have this cover, then you
can get it done there.  You get 45 days of
depression here, so you
can use it twice a year. The total
company will provide this and will give you a necklace,
but here there is a condition that
you will have to clear ten percent of the bill from your pocket, that is,
if the bill is for 10 lakhs, then
you will have to pay nine lakh rupees to the company and
around one lakh from your pocket.
And friends, this is another limitation,
if you had taken 10 lakhs and
you have taken worldwide cover for 10 lakhs, then
you will get 20 lakh rupees, ₹1000000
for your treatment in India and
₹1000000 for your treatment worldwide.
Friends, one good point is the Super No
Claim Bonus.
A Super No Claim Bonus says that
I had just told you earlier that you
get a ten percent no claim bonus under this policy,
which goes up to a maximum of 50%. If you get
this addition and add it under it, then you
The no claim bonus which
you were getting 50%, you will get 50% more here, that is,
50%. If you have a policy of Rs 5 lakh to Rs 10 lakh, then
that 50% will
add up to a maximum of hundred percent. If we
take an example here that you have a policy of Rs 10 lakh, then the
policy of Rs 10 lakh will become
your Chandra Rashi next year if you do
not make any claim and next year again it will become
Rs 2000000 if we do
not make any claim. Okay, and we were getting 10 percent
extra there, then
twenty percent of that will also be added to ours.
But if your policy is between Rs 1500000 to Rs
50 lakh, then you will get 50%
no claim bonus, not up to hundred percent, but two
hundred percent. For example, if
we understand here that I have 20 lakh,
then
fifty percent of 20 lakh Tulsi is 10 lakh,
that means the amount that will be collected in the next year will be
30 lakh.  It will happen, then I did not take a claim of
40 lakhs, then I did not take a claim of 50 lakhs,
then I did not take a claim, then the polish will be of 60 lakh
rupees, friends, and the ones that
we have taken here at the back, if we did not take four-four, then
40 per cent, that one is fine, so
see here how much no claim bonus will be
added to you, as if the premium of your policy was to be paid
there, which is going, so
this feature here is very
useful, friends, if we talk about Hospital Delhi Cantt, then
5 lakhs, if you take a side here, then
why is the minimum in it three
days, that you should have a maximum of 10
days on display, this display should be between three days to
10 days, that is, within about 7 days,
if the hostel superintendent, you will get this and the
money for seven days within it, so if I
talk about 5 lakh airplane, then you will get ₹1000
per day or with and if you have a
plan of 10 lakhs, then you will get ₹2000 per day, that is,
15 lakh to 50 lakhs  If it is a plan then
you will get ₹3000. If you have taken any of these
albums then you will
get its additional benefit. Friends, there are
some other additional benefits of them too, I will
tell you about them. One is the conveyance benefit.
Conveyance benefit is that wherever
your hospital stay goes additional for 10 days
and you have taken this benefit then
this company will give you a lump sum of
Rs.10000. The feature of nursing home is that
friends, wherever the doctor says that
you can take your treatment at home,
you are going after being discharged from the hospital,
which we call post-position,
then after that you may
need a nurse at home. Well, if
any qualified nurse comes to your home
and provides you service, then
here you are in Delhi, then you will get ₹3000.
We will keep giving you reimbursement for that nurse
and the maximum
coverage will be for 15 days. Compassion
and visit  Friends, sometimes
such a situation happens that suppose
you live in another city and your
family lives in another city or it can also happen that
you go to another city for work
and you fall
ill there or have an accident
and you are admitted to the hospital in the same city, then
if in this situation your stay is
more than 5 days, then
your immediate family
members, like children,
parents, if you want to call them from your home to
that city, then whichever
economy class fare or economy class fare will be
reimbursed,
its limit is maximum Rs 20,000, so if you
want to add petrol to it, then you can do it, if we
talk about the investment, friends, the company has made a list of all the items
because I will
give you the details in the description or you will
get the details inside Roshan and if
you suffer from any of those critical illnesses
and you
use this effect cover  It could be as many as four lakh,
five lakh, ten lakh, whatever policy I have,
except for that time, I would have been here.  If it is there then that
money will be deposited in your account.
Suppose you have
taken five lucky positive 5 lakhs critical illness cover for which you will have to pay additional money.
If you get any of these
diseases then you will get treatment. If
you have health insurance of Rs 5 lakhs,
along with this benefit,
a benefit i.e. ₹5 will
also be deposited in your bank account
for which you can use it for the expenses of your family members.
You
can use it for your children's convention or
you can also use it for your father's treatment. Day before yesterday we
talked about accidental cover but yes friends,
under critical illness, Noida is activated
which will be applicable when you have taken the policy, it will
start only after the government date.
After this you have to keep in mind that
if we talk about personal accidental, friends, it is
available only in diet and medical lab.
You will not get these things in children. So whatever personal
accident you have covered here, 5  Regarding the share of Rs 1 lakh to 10
lakh, for example, if
someone dies in an accident, then the
administration takes care of this, then that money and
limited normally goes to the member and
if you have a permanent disability,
friends, that is, like permanently
losing an ankle, losing a hand, losing a leg,
then this tuition is called permanent total
displacement, so in that the
company provides you the entire money,
friends, here we will talk about the explanation of
what are some of the negative points of this plan which are swelled by the company,
so friends, there are some actions in every plan
and it is almost the same here too,
so there is a waiting period of two years, which is
completely exempted, whatever disease
you have declared for it, for example, suppose you
said that I had a hernia problem or
I had a sinus problem or I have
diabetes or I have hypertension, then if
you declare any such unpleasant West Indies, then there is a
waiting period of 2 years in that.
And only after 2 years your problem will be
covered. The second meeting is friends
here like cataract, coriander, joint
replacement, stone, sinus, friends these are such
problems which do not start at one time but over a long period of time,
okay and
in all the companies you will get a waiting period of 2 years for this, in the
first 30 days you will
not get any cover here, you will only get
accidental cover, the company has
added a cover of 2015 equivalent which works only within 15 days,
okay that is wrong, I will
also tell you what that cover is, okay so
after 30 days you understand this policy
will be activated normally, except for accident,
cataract, friends there is a limit here that you will get insurance on
20 thousand rupees, if your
plan is up to ₹5000 which is
needed after 60 years, keep CAT and you will get insurance of 1 lakh
rupees, if your
policy is above 5 lakh rupees, then
friends keeping in mind the crowd, the company has given
some special benefits  Add your power in this
because for this free of cost, some company will
add the child and only tele
consultation is done. Like I
told you earlier that you can consult a Twenty20 doctor.
Okay,
you can also take consultation in this case. The
waiting period which used to be
30 days earlier has been reduced here. The
no claim bonus in this has been
returned under the quality check. If you have that bonus
or not, it does not matter.
After all, here the company has
said that you will take any bonus,
whether it is 1 lakh or three, the bonus in this will not be credited to
your account. It will be
reduced by the committee.
But the bonus that you were supposed to get, whether you have
taken 10%, 20% or 50%, then
you will get it here. Okay,
friends, home health care has also been added here,
that service etc. It says that you, your
doctor, tell us that you have also got something done and
You
need to go topless but you
say no courage, I am
not getting a room inside the hospital, okay or I do
n't want to go to the hospital because the
infection can spread even more there,
so you have to go to the market and there are many
such companies which provide home care services,
here the entire setup of this is installed at home, so
here that service is available
from both cashless and imbursement point of view,
you can email that, the
service of this course
is free of cost till 31 March 2019,
after 31 March 2019 the company will decide whether to
extend this service or not
because they will have to take Idea approval,
if it extends then I will intimate you, so
friends, I have
told you the complete plan, in the upcoming videos
I will reveal the remaining three plans to you as
well, so
friends, I hope you have understood this plan
and if you still have any questions then you can contact
me, my WhatsApp number is
displayed on every screen, so you can contact
me  Whatever it is, you can ask
me in the comment section, you can find my email ID in the
description, you
can ask there also, so
friends, I hope you liked this video,
if you liked it then do
not forget to share it with your friends, do like the video, I will
meet you friends
in the next video, thank you very much for watching this video